Guide to the Papers of Milo Guthrie, 1966-1987 RL.00488
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Material, 1966-1987, undated 4 lin. ft.
  - International Committee for the Defense for African Workers (Box 20)
  - International Feminist Network (Box 20)
  - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War (Box 20)
  - Internationalist Books (Box 20)
  - Inturismo (Box 20)
  - Iowa Union Farmer Association (Box 20)
  - Irish Republican Solidarity Force (Box 20)
  - Island Notes [ecology] (Box 20)
  - John Brown Anti-Klan Committee (Box 20)
  - Johnson County Justice League (Box 20)
  - Jon Wildes Freedom Committee (Box 20)
  - July 4th Coalition [minority rights] (Box 20)
  - Junta of Militant Organizations (Box 20)
  - Kentucky Native American Solidarity Committee (Box 20)
  - Kilusang Mayo Uno (Box 20)
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Box 20)
  - The Knoxville Women's Center (Box 20)
  - Ladybug [ecology] (Box 20)
  - Ladyslipper [catalog of women's music] (Box 20)
  - Lakota Treaty Council [Native American rights] (Box 20)
  - Larry Fox [mail order, custom made items] (Box 20)
  - Lasis [focus on stopping rape] (Box 20)
  - Latin American Diner Theatre (Box 20)
  - Lavender Left Network [gay rights] (Box 20)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights (Box 20)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (Box 20)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 20)
  - Leonard Peltier Defense Committee (Box 20)
  - Lesbian/Gay Boston Town Meeting (Box 20)
  - Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Committee (Box 20)
  - The Lesbian/Gay Taskforce of the El Salvador Initiative Campaign (Box 20)
  - Lesbian and Gay Liberation Taskforce (Box 20)
  - Lesbians Against Police Violence (Box 20)
  - Lesbians and Gays with Kay (Box 20)
  - Lexington Grand Jury Defense Fund Committee (Lexington Six) (Box 20)
  - Liberia del Pueblo (Box 20)
  - Libertarian Party (Box 20)
  - Life Line (Box 20)
  - Line of March (Box 20)
  - Link (newspaper promotion) (Box 20)
  - Livermore Action Group (Box 20)
  - Local 77 Labor Union (Watts Hospital) (Box 20)
  - Local Organizers for Initial Responses to the Kissinger Commission Report (Box 20)
  - Long Branch (Box 20)
  - McSurely Defense Committee (Box 20)
  - Martin Luther King Community Center (Box 20)
  - Medical Aid for El Salvador (Box 20)
  - Memphis Gay Coalition (Box 20)
  - Merit Publishers (Box 20)
  - Metropolitian Community Church of Atlanta (Box 20)
  - Metropolitan Women's Political Caucus (Box 20)
  - Middle Tennessee Land Trust Association (Box 20)
  - Midwest Conference Against the Draft (Box 20)
  - Midwest Student Civil Liberties (Box 20)
  - The Milwaukee Fourteen Defense Committee (Box 20)
  - Moral Hazard [musical group] (Box 20)
  - Moral Majority (Box 20)
  - The Movement (Box 20)
  - Movement in Solidarity with Puerto Rican Independence and Socialism (Box 20)
  - Movimiento de Liberacion Nacional (Box 20)
  - Muncy Correctional Institution (Box 20)
  - Mutual Aid (Box 20)
  - The Naiad Press, Inc. (Box 20)
  - Nashville Coalition of Concerned Citizens (Box 20)
  - Nashville Communities Organized for Progress (Box 20)
  - Nashvillians for a Nuclear Freeze (Box 20)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League (Box 20)
  - National Action/Research on the Military Industrial Complex (Box 20)
  - National Advisory Collective (Box 20)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression (Box 20)
  - National Anti-Draft Network (Box 20)
  - National Anti-Klan Network (Box 20)
  - National Anti-Racist Organizing Committee (Box 20)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box 20)
  - National Black Independent Party (Box 20)
  - National Black Organizer's Conference (Box 20)
  - The National Center for Public Policy Research (Box 20)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (Box 20)
  - National Committee for Peace in Central America (Box 20)
  - National Committee to Abolish HUAC/HISC [an anti-riot act] (Box 20)
  - National Conference on Men and Masculinity (Box 20)
  - National Democratic Policy Committee (Box 20)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (Box 20)
  - National Entertainment Conference (Box 20)
  - The National Federation of Republican Women (Box 20)
  - National Gay Rights Advocates (Box 20)
  - National Indian Youth Council Program (Box 20)
  - National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People (Box 20)
  - National Land for People (Box 20)
  - National Lawyers Guild (Box 20)
  - National May Day Committee (Box 20)
  - The National Mobilization Committee (Box 20)
  - National Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 20)
  - National Mobilization for Survival (Box 20)
  - National Mobilization Headquarters (Box 20)
  - National Network in Solidarity with the Nicaraguan People (Box 20)
  - National Organization for an American Revolution (Box 20)
  - National Organization for Women (Box 20)
  - National Protest Action Plan for Religious Groups (Box 20)
  - National Rainbow Coalition (Box 20)
  - National Resistance Committee (Box 20)
  - National Resistance Conference (Box 20)
  - National Student Labor Action Project (Box 20)
  - National Trade Union Council for Human Rights (Box 20)
  - National Unity Campaign for John Anderson (Box 20)
  - National Welfare Rights Organization (Box 20)
  - Nationwide Unemployed League (Box 20)
  - The Negro Heritage Program (Box 21)
  - New American Movement (Box 21)
  - New Communities Land Debt Retirement Fund (Box 21)
  - New Community Projects (Box 21)
  - New England Free Press (Box 21)
  - New Jersey Conference for the Rights of Migrant Workers (Box 21)
  - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 21)
  - New Modern Movement (Box 21)
  - New Movement in Solidarity with Puerto Rican Independence and Socialism (Box 21)
  - New Outlook Publishers (Box 21)
  - The New Party (Box 21)
  - The New Republic (Box 21)
  - New Society Products, Inc. (Box 21)
  - New Society Publishers (Box 21)
  - New Star Books (Box 21)
  - The New University Conference (Box 21)
  - The Network of Patriotic Letterwriters (Box 21)
  - Nicaragua Network (Box 21)
  - Nicaragua Peace Committee (Box 21)
  - Nicaragua Peace Project (Box 21)
  - North American Bioregional Congress (Box 21)
  - North American Congress on Latin America (Box 21)
  - North Atlantic Books (Box 21)
  - North Carolina Political Prisoners Committee (Box 21)
  - North Carolina Vietnam War Moratorium Committee (Box 21)
  - Northern Neighbors [socialist] (Box 21)
  - November 12 Coalition [anti-US in Central America] (Box 21)
  - Nuclear Free American (Box 21)
  - Nuclear Freeze/Jobs With Peace Campaign (Box 21)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 21)
  - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign (Box 21)
  - Nuke Watch (Box 21)
  - Oasis Center For Human Potential (Box 21)
  - O'Connor, Ms. Egan [concerned citizen about nuclear power] (Box 21)
  - The October League [Marxism] (Box 21)
  - Operation Freedom [black rights] (Box 21)
  - Oral Majority (Box 21)
  - Oregon Womenfolk Core Circle (Box 21)
  - Organizacion de Voluntarios por la Revolucion Puertorriquena (Box 21)
  - Oxfam America (Box 21)
  - Ozark Area Community Congress (Box 21)
  - Palestine Solidarity Committee (Box 21)
  - Pan African Liberation Committee (Box 21)
  - Pathfinder Press (catalog of books) (Box 21)
  - Party of Progressive Socialist Workers (Box 21)
  - Peace and Freedom Party (Box 21)
  - Peace Assembly (Box 21)
  - PeacePac (Box 21)
  - People Against Racism (Box 21)
  - People for a Better Today (Box 21)
  - People United for Justice (Box 21)
  - People's Alliance (Box 21)
  - People's Alliance for a Cooperative Commonwealth (Box 21)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilization (Box 21)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission (Box 21)
  - People's Energy Campaign (Box 21)
  - People's Party (Box 21)
  - People's World (magazine promotion) (Box 21)
  - Philaposh [political buttons designers] (Box 21)
  - Planners Inc. (Box 21)
  - Polaroid Revolutionary Movement (Box 21)
  - Political Education Committee (Box 21)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (Box 21)
  - Prairie Fire (Box 21)
  - Praxis [socialist action union at Duke University] (Box 21)
  - Pride Committee [gay rights] (Box 21)
  - Progressive Education (Box 21)
  - Progressive Labor Party (Box 21)
  - Prolifers for Survival (Box 21)
  - Prometheus Paperbacks (Box 21)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace (Box 21)
  - Provisional World Parliament (Box 21)
  - Public Interest Research (Box 21)
  - Quaker Action Group (Box 21)
  - Quaker House (Box 21)
  - Quest (Box 21)
  - Quixote Center (Box 21)
  - Radical Eduction Project (Box 21)
  - Radical Fairies [gay men] (Box 21)
  - Radical Organizing Committee (Box 21)
  - Ray O. Light [black liberation] (Box 21)
  - Reagan For Shah Committee (Box 21)
  - Reclaiming Our Magic [worship of the Great Goddess] (Box 21)
  - Recon Publications (Box 21)
  - Red Dragon (letters to this magazine) (Box 21)
  - Red Lily Distributors (Box 21)
  - Refugees of Resurrection City USA (Box 21)
  - Religious Task Force on Central America (Box 21)
  - Republican Party (Box 21)
  - Resist (Box 21)
  - The Resistance (Box 21)
  - Resistencia Puertorriquena (Box 21)
  - Resource Center for Non-Violence (Box 21)
  - Revolutionary Communist Party, USA (Box 21)
  - Revolutionary Socialist League (Box 21)
  - Revolutionary Union (Box 21)
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement (Box 21)
  - RFD (magazine promotion) (Box 21)
  - Richmond Committee for Jobs, Not War (Box 21)
  - Rising Up Angry (magazine promotion) (Box 21)
  - Rita Silk-Nauni Defense Committee (Box 21)
  - Riverside Church Disarmament Program (Box 21)
  - Rocky Flats Petition Campaign (Box 21)
  - Rural Cumberland Resources (Box 21)
  - Sacred Mountain Alliance (Box 21)
  - Safe Forms of Energy for Tennessee (Box 21)
  - Salvadorean Humanitarian Aid Research and Education Foundation (Box 21)
  - San Francisco Aids Foundation (Box 21)
  - San Francisco Lesbian and Gay Men's community Chorus (Box 21)
  - SANE [nuclear freeze] (Box 21)
  - "Sanity Now!" (Box 21)
  - Savannah River Peace Encampment (Box 21)
  - Save the Planet Campaign (Box 21)
  - Sawicki and Son (mail order catalog) (Box 21)
  - Scoop Collective (Box 21)
  - Seminole Nation of Oklahoma (Box 21)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee (Box 21)
  - September Women's Action (Box 21)
  - The Service Committee (Box 21)
  - Shelby Park Community Center (Box 21)
  - Shell Strike Support Committee (Box 21)
  - Sierra Club (Box 21)
  - Simmons Brother's Defense Committee (Box 21)
  - Simple Co-op (Box 21)
  - Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence [gay men] (Box 21)
  - Social Science Institute (Box 21)
  - Socialist Action Union (Box 21)
  - Socialist Caucus of the Kentucky Women's Political Caucus (Box 21)
  - Socialist Committee of Correspondence (Box 21)
  - Socialist Labor Party (Box 21)
  - Socialist League for Industrial Government (Box 21)
  - Socialist Party, USA (Box 21)
  - The Socialist Road (magazine promotion) (Box 21)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Box 21)
  - The Solar Lobby (Box 21)
  - Solidarity Party (Box 21)
  - Solidarity Publications (Box 21)
  - Soma Direct (Box 21)
  - Sonoma County Peace Network (Box 21)
  - South End Press (Box 21)
  - Southeastern Conference of Lesbians and Gay Men (Box 21)
  - Southern Africa Anti-Mercenary Coalition (Box 21)
  - Southern California Coalition for a National Health Service (Box 21)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund (Box 21)
  - Southern Conference on World Affairs (Box 22)
  - Southern Institute for Propaganda and Organizing (Box 22)
  - Southern Legal Action Movement (Box 22)
  - Southern Mountains Bookstore (Box 22)
  - Southern Organizing Committee for Economic and Social Justice (Box 22)
  - Southern Regional Council, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Box 22)
  - Soviet Life (magazine promotion) (Box 22)
  - Soviet Peace Committee (Box 22)
  - Spartacist League (Box 22)
  - Special Delivery Army [anti-communist group] (Box 22)
  - The Statehood Party (Box 22)
  - Stern, Nanci [poet] (Box 22)
  - Stop Cruise (Box 22)
  - Stop the Road (Box 22)
  - Strawberry Hill Press (Box 22)
  - Student Liberation Front (Box 22)
  - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 22)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (Box 22)
  - Student Peace Union (Box 22)
  - Students and Labor (Box 22)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (Box 22)
  - Susanna Ounei Tour Committee (Box 22)
  - Survival Week (Box 22)
  - Syracuse Cultural Workers (mail order catalog) (Box 22)
  - Take Back the Night March Coalition (Box 22)
  - Tax Conversion Fund for Peace and Human Needs (Box 22)
  - Temporary Organizing Committee for a Marxist-Leninist Youth Organization (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Association of Planned Parenthood Affiliates, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Catfish Alliance (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Citizens for Wilderness Planning (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Gay Coalition for Human Rights (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Hunger Coalition (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Nuclear Waste Task Force (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Peace and Disarmament Campaign (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Rainbow Coalition (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 22)
  - Tennessee Valley Socialists (Box 22)
  - Tennesseans Keeping Abortion Legal and Safe (Box 22)
  - Texas Labor Fund (Box 22)
  - Third Ward Statehood Clubs (Box 22)
  - Thundergoat Press (Box 22)
  - The Tobacco Workers Union (Box 22)
  - The Tobacco Workers Voluntary Organizing Committee (Box 22)
  - Triangle Friends of the United Farm Workers (Box 22)
  - Twin Cities draft Information Center (Box 22)
  - Uhuru House/Uhuru Solidarity Center (Box 22)
  - The Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 22)
  - United Citizens for Peace (Box 22)
  - United Nations (Box 22)
  - United Peoples Socialist Party (Box 22)
  - United States--China Peoples Friendship Alliance (Box 22)
  - United States Farmers Association (Box 22)
  - United States Friends of the Salvadorean Revolution (Box 22)
  - United States National Student Association (Box 22)
  - United States of America Green Party (Box 22)
  - United States out of Central America (Box 22)
  - Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches (Box 22)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Black Student Movement, 1969 (Box 22)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Cafeteria Boycott, 1969 (Box 22)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Saga Strike, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Upshot (Box 22)
  - Urban Underground (Box 22)
  - Vancouver Centre New Democrats (Box 22)
  - Venceremos Brigade (Box 22)
  - Vermont Telephone Boycott Committee (Box 22)
  - Veterans for Peace in Vietnam (Box 22)
  - Vietnam Moratorium Committee (Box 22)
  - Vietnam Solidarity Campaign (Box 22)
  - Vietnam Statement (Box 22)
  - Vietnam Summer (Box 22)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War--Winter Soldier Organization, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Vocations for Social Change (Box 22)
  - War Resisters League (Box 22)
  - Washington Coalition Against Prisons (Box 22)
  - Washington Mobilization for Peace (Box 22)
  - The Washington Peace Center (Box 22)
  - W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of New York (Box 22)
  - Win Magazine (Box 22)
  - Wisconsin Alliance Farm Brigades (Box 22)
  - Wisconsin Civil Liberties Union (Box 22)
  - Wisconsin Independent People's Party (Box 22)
  - Woman to Woman Campaign (Box 22)
  - Women Against Military Madness (Box 22)
  - Women for Impeachment (Box 22)
  - Women in Distribution, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Women Strike for Peace (Box 22)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 22)
  - Women's Irish Boycott Army (Box 22)
  - Women's Peace Encampment (Box 22)
  - Womyn Make Waves for Peace (Box 22)
  - Work and Pay Committee (Box 22)
  - Workers Action Movement (Box 22)
  - Workers Viewpoint (Box 22)
  - Workers World (Box 22)
  - Workers World Party (Box 22)
  - World Constitution and Parliament Association (Box 22)
  - World Events (Box 22)
  - World Events Committee (Box 22)
  - World Federalist Association (Box 22)
  - World Magazine (Box 22)
  - World Policy Institute (Box 22)
  - World View Publishers (Box 22)
  - Yard Roots (magazine promotion) (Box 22)
  - Young Patriots Organization (Box 22)
  - The Young People's Socialist League (Box 22)
  - Young Socialist Alliance (Box 22)
  - Young Workers' Liberation League (Box 22)
  - Youth Against War and Fascism (Box 22)
  - Youth for a New America (Box 22)
  - Youth International Party (Box 22)
  - Youth Liberation (Box 22)
  - Zed Books (Box 22)